Yeah!
Moooa! Yeah!
- Why is that a good reaction? - Are you okay?
Whoa!
Stop it!
Kosaka Presents: Live Game Show
Okay, so it's been a while since I've done a live game show, but here's the girl who's going to be doing it with me this time around.
This time, we have a girl who will be playing a game with us!
Wow, Hinatazaka 46!
I see...
That's right!
I'm Nanami Konishi, a student in the 464th class of Hinatazaka46.
Konishi.
Today... why did I call you Konishi?
Yes...
I don't know...
Something... something...
He said he wanted to play a horror game.
I've always wanted to try it.
So this time, I'm going to ask Konishi to play a horror game!
I heard you like ghost stories.
I like ghost stories.
I like to listen to them.
But I've never actually played a game with such stories.
I'm too scared to do it visually.
Konishi has just the game for you!
It's perfect for you!
Let's play together!
Thank you very much.
Now, what I'd like you to play this time, Konishi...
This Tsugu no Hi, Dusk and Dawn, Parallel Train.
What is it?
This game is
It's a game that even a horror novice can easily handle.
Basically, all you have to do is to go to the left.
It is a horror game
It's a horror game
but it is still a horror game.
There is a horror element, too.
It is a game about a girl's way back to her station on the train
so it's a game about that.
I see.
So, let's start the game, shall we?
Press "ENT" to start.
Here we go.
It's growing!
It's growing so much!
Oh, wow!
There's a horror story in there.
Please be careful.
Is this Enter?
Enter.
It's covered in blood.
What is this?
I've never played computer games before.
I see. It's my first time.
It's so realistic.
Left key to move.
Enter key to send text.
It's all train stuff.
You can press enter for this.
I see you have a cell phone.
Yes, there's a phone, too.
That's great.
LOL
A little hunched over.
Just like me.
Konishi himself.
Enter, I guess.
That's amazing.
It's so realistic.
It's amazing.
The font is scary.
We have to go through the next station.
Let's move to the street closer to the turnstiles.
The one closest to the turnstiles.
You've thought this through, haven't you?
There.
It's going.
Do I have to keep pushing this?
All the way to the left.
I'm scared.
Are the ads too scary?
I wouldn't take a train in the morning like this.
I'm scared.
It's amazing how everyone on the train looks so mysterious.
I can't see their faces.
Is this something that's going to appear?
Let's keep going.
Every step we take is scary.
It's pretty scary.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's go.
Is this the train next to us, or is it a parallel train?
Yes, it is.
There are a lot of black people on it.
Are they looking at us?
This train is full of people.
They're running side by side.
Is this game over or something?
I can do the basics.
Are you sure?
Let's go to the ticket gate.
You're right.
It's okay.
Don't do anything.
I wonder if it's ready yet.
It's close to the ticket gate.
A train is a long car.
Yes, they are.
It's a schoolboy.
It's the first time I've seen a person in the back of the train.
Every time I live here, he runs alongside me.
The train next to me...
It's a title parallel train.
That kind of thing
Four Seasons, Four Wings
Grandpa
What?
You were reading the newspaper.
He's reading from the front.
I'm going to look at it so much!
This is going pretty fast.
What's wrong?
Oh, the armored train is moving fast!
Too fast!
It's shaking a lot. Are you okay?
Guys, don't look at your phones!
That's for sure!
They're not looking at me.
I've never seen anyone in a mask before.
That's pretty realistic.
The drawings.
It really looks like he's here.
Is this close to the turnstiles?
A man.
Is it here?
This is it.
Right here.
He's got a great profile.
There's a guy blocking the screen.
It's half closed.
Half a man.
That doesn't happen very often.
I don't even have eyes in my face.
Basically.
You're right... they do have facial expressions.
I can't see their eyes.
Okay, it's open.
Is this Enter?
Enter.
We're here.
Oh, is that a success?
Game clear.
Game Clear
Open.
Isn't that the sound of the next day? Definitely.
It's like repeating several days like this.
I see, so it was hard work from the very first day.
What? Next station already?
We're getting close to the turnstiles again today.
It's going to move a little bit faster.
It's been a long day.
Yes.
There's someone else on the train.
It's like that in some places.
It's different from yesterday.
Oh, here come the armaments!
Here comes the armada!
Wow, uncle's face.
It's kind of bad.
I don't remember it being like this.
I've never seen it before.
I've never seen human eyes before.
I'm not on it
And the woman standing in front of it is a little dangerous
I hope she's okay.
Uh-oh.
I'm so scared.
I wonder if she's okay... she doesn't look good... she doesn't look good... she doesn't look good... she doesn't look white?
There's a purple high-school girl in a sailor suit... and she's totally different from yesterday... and the person on the train is scary.
I'm scared. It's half of the car.
What's that? Sailor-suited girls on the same side of the train...
Same school? Kids.
Same school.
Oh, she's sleeping. Mom's asleep.
Oh, it stopped.
It's linked! With the train in disguise.
It's true. It's true.
What's this? A girl, too.
Oh, a pale old man.
He's on it. He's on that one, too.
Oh, my God, there's a very disturbing sound.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
That's a good reaction.
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm scared, scared, scared.
Yes, I'm afraid.
Yay!
I did it.
What's that?
Turn around a little bit.
What's wrong?
I couldn't stand up normally.
I hope you don't feel bad.
It's a girl in a sailor suit.
I wonder if she'll arrive before the end of the day.
She's laughing.
I can hear her laughing.
Like my laugh.
That was me when I folded the house alone.
What?
What do you mean?
You're laughing alone in the house?
Yes, I am.
I think that might be the scariest thing I've heard all day.
That's what I'm talking about.
I don't know if anyone's watching this.
I'm scared.
Is the sky a little dark in here?
Yeah, it is.
It's not dark at night or anything.
Another person.
But this one...
He was here first.
You were here first.
What do you mean?
What do you mean? My eyes are getting all red.
I think it's following us.
No, like this.
Like a bedbug.
Betven.
I'm so sorry.
He's apologizing so much!
But there's an old man on the train.
He's so pale.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Next door!
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
He's apologizing so much!
He stopped.
Oh, no!
The girl in the sailor suit is cute!
I'm looking at her!
From the train.
She's smiling.
What the heisei era clothes!
I miss this kind of clothes.
The girl's face.
Shoulders?
Shoulders? I'm grabbing her shoulder.
He's holding her shoulder.
Wait, that's a lot of information.
Sleeping?
He's kind of cute.
Tension?
She's your mother, isn't she?
She's looking at me like I'm crazy.
I've never seen anyone like this before.
It stopped.
What's going on? There's no one else on the train.
I'm scared, scared, scared, scared.
He's staring at me.
I'm not reading a book.
My mouth.
Are you okay?
I wonder if he's even aware of what's going on.
He didn't notice.
He's so unperturbed.
He's fine.
I'm scared.
Is the disguised train stopping too?
I've never seen this before.
That's a first.
That's the first time a train in disguise has stopped.
I've never seen a disguise train stop at a disguise train before.
What does this mean?
Wow.
kills
주
ee ee ee
Surprise vary
Eeeeee ne ue
Really
It's the worst.
The guy who just came in...
I'm getting off at the next station.
You shouldn't take this train.
It's about time. It's the only way home.
That's right.
The woman again. Wasn't she reading a book?
She was reading.
She's just looking at me.
She's staring at me.
She's even wearing it around her neck.
Yes, yes, yes.
Who was that?
Uncle Dan comes over regularly.
He's coming.
The kid from before is behind you.
He laughed
Watch out.
I've never seen you in a hoodie before.
Are there a lot of girls following you?
They're staring at you.
They're staring at me like crazy.
The kid's shoulders.
They're getting more and more crooked.
And the mother...
Mother.
Yes, ma'am.
You scared me.
She's gone crazy.
What the hell?
It's the kids! The kids!
He's laughing so hard!
Hey...
I can't open this door.
Oh, no!
What am I going to do?
What's going on?
Is it broken?
What?
Don't do that.
Don't do it.
This is it. We still have to go.
Don't walk any further.
No more walking.
Oh, my God, Grandpa's face is getting really scary.
It's absolutely crazy. Oh, everyone's like this.
Everyone's eyes are like this, everyone's eyes are funny.
It's not good. It's not good.
It's bad!
Let's move on!
He's smiling.
Stop it, stop it, Grandpa.
Grandpa, the newspaper guy who left, he's here and he's back.
This grandpa is too funny.
Ooh.
Woo.
Oh, great.
Whoa! Vehicle, can we go to the next vehicle?
Oh, no, we're not there yet.
Oh, I'm scared.
But this guy's still kind of...
Red, are his eyes turning red?
Huh! Wait, I'm pretty sure that's me! He's on the train.
He's gone.
He's over there.
I'm sure!
Oh, yeah...
He's on the move!
This, this kid is pretty current.
This kid is bad.
This is bad.
Oh, he's stopped.
It's stuck?
Why?
We can't stop here.
I'm scared!
Horror, horror, horror!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
I've sent you the weirdest thing I've ever seen.
Here we go...
Is this your turn?
Not here!
Not here yet?
Oh, that's good.
I can't do it!
I can't do it.
He's looking at me.
He's staring at me. He's staring at me.
It's a girl.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm being drawn in.
I've never seen her before.
This girl.
What is it?
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
She's looking at me.
She's looking at me like crazy.
Oh, no.
Oh, there's no more parallel trains.
Let's go to the countryside.
Let's go to the country.
Oh, we've lost the train.
Come to the country? What do you mean, back there?
What's that? It's not the usual scenery.
I missed the train before I knew it. I have to get off at the next stop.
Oh, I see. We're still going.
No, I'm afraid, afraid, afraid, afraid... of nothing.
And lust... it's true.
Not even close...
I hate anamos, it's on the left
Oh, I'm here, I'm here, I'm a little more scared of anamos
It might happen again
We're here... I'm scared...
What's this? What does it mean?
Oh, no, don't go down that way! It's red!
There are so many red people!
Are you going to ride it again?
Not the next day, the next day.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What? Are you okay?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, we have to get off at the next stop.
Is it too red outside?
It's bad outside.
It's bad, isn't it?
And the train.
What do you mean?
That's funny.
Just notice it.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
She's smiling so much.
The woman.
Is she fading?
I was outside.
She's smiling.
You're scaring me.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a hole in the train.
Why?
The train is getting worse and worse.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is crazy...
Oh my God, this wash house.
It's got this hole in it.
The girls can peek through all the holes.
What is this?
What do you want?
It's definitely this girl.
If this thing is transparent...
What does that mean?
They're probably all down.
Mom, they're not here.
Are you okay?
You scared me.
I'm home.
He says he's home.
What does that mean?
Mr. Newspaper.
What? I don't have a newspaper.
High-grade canned food.
You're too scary, kitty!
Mister...
Uncle!
Uncle and Grandma are all behind me.
What's this all about?
Wait!
What is it?
Oh, my God!
What? You mean the strap is your hand?
He's going for it.
Oh, shit.
What? What's going on?
They're staring at us.
Everyone's peeking.
They're laughing.
What's so funny?
Oh, no!
Grandpa, you fell down.
It's not leather anymore.
Simple old man!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
He's staring at me.
It's amazing.
He's peeking a little.
It's weird.
Just on the top of his head.
Oh, really?
What is that?
Outside.
Oh, it's huge, huge, huge!
That's amazing.
I'm scared.
I can't take it anymore.
Look, it's getting bigger and bigger!
This is it, this is it, it's going.
Look, it's getting closer!
It's going away! It's going away!
You marshmallow!
Two school kids now...
Are you okay? Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Watch out!
I'm sorry.
It's getting worse, isn't it?
It's just...
It's normal.
I'm sorry, Uncle.
I'm sorry.
Uncle I'm sorry.
It's been a long time.
That's great, great, great, great, great, great!
I'm sorry, Uncle.
My hand, my hand, my hand, my hand!
Wow!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's too much information, too much information.
I can go into it now.
I'm done, I'm here.
I'm here. - Mouth half open.
What?
What? What do you mean?
What? What is it? What is it?
What is that?
What's that?
That?
My...
Why am I over there?
What?
Yeah, why?
But this...
What train am I on?
What? This one.
Where is this train going?
What? What?
I got on the right side.
I'm sure.
Oh, my God, I fell off.
Are you okay?
Oh, it's all black.
Is this...
Are you saying it's happening all over again?
You mean he's gone the other way?
It's gone.
Wow!
It's a surprisingly good story.
Yes, it's true. It repeats itself.
It's the kind of thing that repeats itself.
I was surprised that I reacted the way I did.
I was surprised at myself.
It was interesting.
The last time I went in the next day
I was surprised at myself.
Upstream
I was like, "Wow!
I was so surprised that I couldn't even be surprised
Ohasuge ohasuge!
It was like a fever, wasn't it?
Oh, he's already over there!
It's true, he's asking for help!
Oops!
It resonated.
This girl's eyes turned red, too.
Which one is true?
People who are obsessed turn red.
Maybe that's what I'm saying.
You don't even know you're in it.
Wow.
How was it?
It was my first time to play a horror game, but it was surprisingly fun, and I wasn't alone,
And, since Mr. Kasagawa was there, I was able to finish the game happily.
I'm glad I did.
Your reactions were really funny.
I was scared. I was scared, but Konishi shouted at me, so I shifted my reaction to funny.
Was that a good thing?
But you know, it's easy to play even for beginners.
It was really easy to play, just by moving forward.
I think it's a great game for beginners, so please try it!
If you like this video, please give it a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
Bye bye!
by H.